uh
You put my name in flashing lights You love the
story, you love the fights You called me pure,
you called me clean Another part of your 16 I am
not your victim I am not your saint I'm the
monster that you try to paint I am not your
status, I am not your grace I'm the one who's
spinning in your face
You left the trial, the family torn The
wholesome girl, so sad and worn You never
stopped to ask me What I was fighting just to be
Your victim, I am not your saint I'm the monster
that you try to paint I am not your stardust, I am
not your grace I'm the one who's spitting in your
face I'm not a victim I'm not a saint I am a weapon
Oh.
I am not your victim, I am not your saint I'm the
monster that you try to paint I am not your
stardust, I am not your grace I'm the one who's
spitting in your face